scanning 352 transcripts...
352 transcripts read, 0 unreadable, 195 candidate moments

  1. score   9.0  RzjGikNbHMA  @2:26  (140s)
     let me stop you, here's the thing, let me ask you, personal riff, consequences, not feeling you
     https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=RzjGikNbHMA&t=8795s
     > >> I mean >> Wait, let me let me just tell you consequences and about consequences,
       right? >> Yes, ma'am. >> I'm a firm believer in consequences for actions, right? >>
       Absolutely. >> So, if you don't want to tell me, that's fine. You know what's going
       to end up happening? >> No, I don't. >> But no, no, no, I'm going to just tell you.
       I'll accept your pleas, and then I'm going to say, we're going to come back, I'm
       going to send you to go get drug tested, and we're going to come back for results.
       So, I mean, if you want to take that route, we can take that route. >> Okay. >> So,
       before we even s

  2. score   8.0  zHchVGBX9iA  @2:58  (100s)
     let me stop you, smells like, personal riff, guess what
     https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=zHchVGBX9iA&t=10715s
     > who comes in, I can smell cigarette smoke on them. You can chew all the spearmint gum
       you want, then you just smell like spearmint gum and cigarette smoke. I don't drink.
       Why I don't drink? I just don't think it tastes good. It tastes nasty to me. Anybody
       who walks up in here and they've had an alcoholic beverages, they can spray their
       mouth, they can swish some mouthwash. Guess what? I smell still smell alcohol cuz I
       don't do alcohol. I don't do cigarette smoke. I can just My sense of smell is highly
       elevated. I guarantee you your child goes to school, other children who don't have
       parents

  3. score   7.0  5JCXUxS08U4  @0:52  (60s)
     guess what, let me stop you, excuse me
     https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=5JCXUxS08U4&t=3135s
     > He said no. And let me just tell you, here's a perfect example. And I' I've been in
       situations where people have told me no. And my thing is, I want you to not send me
       place to place. If the answer is no, just tell me no and I'll figure it out. He told
       you no. If I ask him right now, like for example, I had to rush here this morning cuz
       I don't like being late and I was filling in for somebody else on another matter and
       guess what? My tank is at a fourth. I don't like it being at a fourth. Now, would
       somebody go, "Excuse me, could you go and put

  4. score   7.0  JDwlO34WOa8  @1:08  (60s)
     are you serious, let me ask you, personal riff
     https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=JDwlO34WOa8&t=4115s
     > so I feel like at times it's not always good like I don't make enough or it's just a
       lot like I pay my car I take care of my grandparents. It's just a lot like and I get
       it's not legal and it's not an excuse but I don't smoke all the time like I was
       telling her I don't do heavy drugs. Like I don't do nothing bad and I get it's still
       not legal but >> it's just a lot of stuff like going on in my personal life. >> All
       right. So let me ask you this. Do you think I have stressors? >> Pretty sure. >>
       Yeah. I mean, I have a lot of stressors, right? >> I'm pretty sure a lot. >> So,
       because I do this,

  5. score   7.0  MFqdWnZNfWA  @2:31  (80s)
     here's the thing, you're an adult, guess what
     https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=MFqdWnZNfWA&t=9055s
     > be going from parents house to parents house. And I'm going to tell you what I tell
       everybody who is an adult or living with somebody else. If you want to keep a dirty
       kitchen, you can keep a dirty kitchen. But guess what? It needs to be your dirty
       kitchen. So whether you're an adult or not, whether you're 21 or 60, if you're living
       under somebody else's roof, you need to follow their rules. You understand? They're
       asking for a MC evaluation. Is there any prior mental health issues? No, I'm still in
       my left ear. I'm sorry. He has physical deformity, judge. He can't hear out of his
       left ear. Ok

  6. score   7.0  pgHDPyKdcQs  @0:05  (80s)
     let me stop you, here's the thing, answer the question, being honest
     https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=pgHDPyKdcQs&t=315s
     > when people test positive, right? But part of being in recovery and trying to be in
       recovery is honesty. Yes, that's it. And I asked you if you're going to be positive
       and what you presented to the court that you would be only positive for
       prescriptions. >> for your prescriptions. So, were you positive for more than your
       prescriptions? Yes, it shows that I am positive for more than prescriptions. All
       right. Well, I mean, we're not talking about what it shows. That's what I mean about
       being honest. And I have relapsed, but it's been a matter of time. Um that's what I
       meant by not perfection. I

  7. score   6.5  A0ELrUxbUe0  @0:16  (60s)
     here's the thing, let me ask you, personal riff
     https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=A0ELrUxbUe0&t=995s
     > Third >> first one, I did the time. >> Second one, the levels were low. The way they
       stopped me. >> Let me ask you this. Do you know how many driving while intoxicated
       charges I have? >> No. >> Yeah. Now, I don't drink alcohol because I think it tastes
       nasty. But I don't even drink that. I think it's nasty. So, yeah. So, here's the
       problem. Do you know my mom had us listen to this preacher? because you know
       preachers tell stories in church and they were talking about this guy and his mom
       would always be there to get him out of trouble. And so fast forward, he's in
       trouble. He's at the jail and

  8. score   6.5  gykk7wZIdJ4  @1:11  (60s)
     grown man/woman, you're an adult, make better decisions
     https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=gykk7wZIdJ4&t=4255s
     > own or possess any weapons or ammunition. If you have a question over what a weapon
       or ammunition is, you'll need to speak to an attorney. Do you understand? See? Yes.
       All right, we can go off the record. You're going to have to make better choices.
       What you did, those were not mistakes. Those were horrible choices. You're a grown
       man. You're an adult. You're supposed to be setting example for your children. You
       understand? All right. Everyone uh wants you to be successful on this probation. If I
       didn't think you could complete it, I would tell them I would not follow this
       agreement. So, if th

  9. score   6.0  7JFazJ9tbiQ  @0:54  (40s)
     let me stop you, here's the thing, excuse me
     https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=7JFazJ9tbiQ&t=3235s
     > I've been back to state Texas for seven months >> where were you before >> I was in
       Sana I had >> I'm sorry where >> I was in North Carolina for >> Excuse me everyone
       Please whisper >> for the last 11 years up until this year in the state of North
       Carolina with the job. >> No, here's the thing. >> Were they coming off that? >> So,
       were you in the were you in Bexar County on April 20 I'm sorry, April 23rd, 2026?
       Because that's the date of this offense. >> But it was a trespass. >> No, no, no. It
       was not. Let me just tell you what the facts of this case are. You were in a park.

 10. score   6.0  BZU-54HjqSQ  @1:41  (60s)
     let me stop you, here's the thing, excuse me
     https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=BZU-54HjqSQ&t=6075s
     > good. How are you? >> Oh, I'm doing great. You know, I was people were saying, "Oh,
       are you team Jeremiah or a Conrad or something?" >> Who's that? I don't know. >>
       That's what I'm saying. I'm like, "Who >> is there a pop culture thing that I'm
       missing out on?" >> It's something about the the summer I turned pretty or something.
       >> Oh, is it a TV? >> It's always like a good guy and then the other one is kind of
       like a bad boy. >> But here's the thing. My understanding now that somebody's told me
       they're brothers, right? >> Oh, >> hey, let me just tell you, my mom would have put a
       stop to that

 11. score   6.0  N6hDpprKobk  @0:23  (60s)
     guess what, mumbling
     https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=N6hDpprKobk&t=1375s
     > that's unrelated to this trial. I just want everyone to make sure that you focus on
       the trial. Does everyone understand? All right. So, the parties have stood up and
       introduced themselves to you. And even the people who are just here to learn, raise
       your card if you recognize any of the parties who've introduced themselves to you.
       All right. So, no one has raised their cards. To my left is the court reporter. Cindy
       takes down everything that everyone is saying. That can be difficult. The reason why
       it can be difficult is because guess what? Some people want to mumble.

 12. score   6.0  QfKjHJ1A4KM  @3:00  (60s)
     let me ask you, are you doing this, here's the thing
     https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=QfKjHJ1A4KM&t=10795s
     > >> All right. Is that the proposed agreement? >> It is your honor. >> All right. Let
       me ask you something. Do you want to go to prison? >> Then why are you doing this? >>
       Bad decisions. >> No, I mean here's the thing. You have decisions that you have to
       make. And on the one hand, your decision is, do I want to do this? If I do this and
       I'm caught, I could look at life in prison. And then what ends up happening is your
       attorney has a and this is where

