352 transcripts | LONG judicial turns 1584 | SHORT 2834

phrase                                        long  short    lift
no employment as a                             130      0   465.2
no employment as                               130      0   465.2
employment as a                                130      0   465.2
no employment as a home                        129      0   461.6
employment as a home                           129      0   461.6
as a home                                      129      0   461.6
health care provider                           127      0   454.4
home health care                               126      0   450.9
home health care provider                      125      0   447.3
employment as a home health                    124      0   443.7
as a home health care                          124      0   443.7
as a home health                               124      0   443.7
a home health care provider                    124      0   443.7
a home health care                             124      0   443.7
a home health                                  124      0   443.7
proof of employment within                     115      0   411.5
of employment within                           115      0   411.5
employment within days                         115      0   411.5
proof of employment within days                113      0   404.3
of employment within days                      113      0   404.3
care provider or                               113      0   404.3
provider or with minors                        112      0   400.8
provider or with                               112      0   400.8
or with minors                                 112      0   400.8
health care provider or                        112      0   400.8
home health care provider or                   111      0   397.2
care provider or with minors                   110      0   393.6
care provider or with                          110      0   393.6
health care provider or with                   109      0   390.0
one time per                                   103      0   368.6
visits one time                                101      0   361.4
visits one time per                             98      0   350.7
visits one time per month                       97      0   347.1
time per month                                  97      0   347.1
one time per month                              97      0   347.1
days no employment as a                         82      0   293.4
days no employment as                           82      0   293.4
days no employment                              82      0   293.4
within days no employment as                    81      0   289.8
within days no employment                       81      0   289.8
within days no                                  81      0   289.8
of employment within days no                    76      0   271.9
employment within days no employment            76      0   271.9
employment within days no                       76      0   271.9
field visits one time                           71      0   254.1
field visits one                                71      0   254.1
field visits one time per                       68      0   243.3
service restitution i'm going to                66      0   236.2
service restitution i'm going                   66      0   236.2
service restitution i'm                         66      0   236.2
restitution i'm going to                        66      0   236.2
restitution i'm going                           66      0   236.2
community service restitution i'm going         66      0   236.2
community service restitution i'm               66      0   236.2
at the time                                     64      0   229.0
suspended and probated for                      63      0   225.4
and probated for                                63      0   225.4
restitution i'm going to order                  62      0   221.9
per month for                                   62      0   221.9
unsupervised contact with                       61      0   218.3
no unsupervised contact with                    61      0   218.3
no unsupervised contact                         61      0   218.3
unsupervised contact with minors                60      0   214.7
no unsupervised contact with minors             60      0   214.7
contact with minors                             60      0   214.7
time per month for                              59      0   211.1
one time per month for                          59      0   211.1
out of custody                                  58      0   207.5
of community service restitution i'm            58      0   207.5
prison suspended and probated for               55      0   196.8
uas proof of employment                         54      0   193.2
uas proof of                                    54      0   193.2
you to years in the                             50      0   178.9
i want to                                       50      0   178.9
evaluation out of custody                       49      0   175.3
evaluation out of                               49      0   175.3
uas proof of employment within                  48      0   171.8
time and money                                  48      0   171.8
one of the                                      48      0   171.8
tap evaluation out of custody                   46      0   164.6


=== 6 LONGEST RIFFS FOUND (raw) ===

-- aDPB0h45QIM @4011s  (3620 words)
   https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=aDPB0h45QIM&t=4006s
   That's his mom. All right, so that's Mr. De La Rosa's mom. Courtrooms are to be open to the public, so anybody who wants to come in and watch, they're welcome to come in and watch. So, she's not participating. She's not going to be asking questions of you all. She's just here to watch this process. Does everyone understand? Yes. All right. So, now the charge in this case is aggravated assault with a deadly weapon. Normally, people say, "You know what? I would love if I could get a accident case where it's next door at the historic courthouse." But, in order to have jury trials, we need jurors. Does everyone understand? Yes. And before I go further uh into this case, you've had a chance to have the parties stand and introduce themselves. Is there anyone here who recognizes any of the parties? If you do, please raise your card. All right. Now, I've told you the charge is aggravated assault

-- 9hW7kh5WCsA @8032s  (3624 words)
   https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=9hW7kh5WCsA&t=8027s
   Yes. Correct. Yes. Yes. Another photo of the firearm that was located in the vehicle. Yes, it's an overhead view of looking through the holster that's actually the barrel of or a muzzle of the firearm. What is depicted in that photo? This is the another tire with the damages to the bumper area. The rear I believe that's the rear back driver's wheel with the depiction of the TID's paintings. That is the drop of the iPhone that was located in the driver's seat. Yes, it is. And is that another photo of the victim in the master bedroom? Yes, it is. What is depicted in So, I've backed I'm to the right or the south of the vehicle. You'll notice that it's on the other side of those reflect highly reflective signs there. And it's just a a further view or angle of that vehicle and how it's positioned to the wall. And then regarding the railing that we see, do you know if it's located in that buil

-- T4NeST9PD9Y @3831s  (3356 words)
   https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=T4NeST9PD9Y&t=3826s
   Your Honor, I'm going to object I'm going to object to that because that was a mis- that's a mischaracterization with the evidence was. Antonio Lerma did not say that the defendant was intoxicated. He did not testify. All right, ladies and gentlemen, you will remember the evidence the way you recall it. Does everyone understand? All right, you may proceed. Now, I want to talk to you about the timeline of what the defense witnesses are asking you to believe, right? Because if you listen to the defendant's word, he's saying that he only consumed one beer at 7:30 p.m. Okay? But, if you listen to Jared, he says that the defendant consumed an alcoholic beverage at 9:00 p.m. That would have been while they were at El Camino, and you can look at those receipts that are in evidence to confirm that. But, the video is everything, and we'll get back to that. Now, he knows that the brick at Blue Sta

-- XVr9aknFQ9E @656s  (3027 words)
   https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=XVr9aknFQ9E&t=651s
   A person acts recklessly or is reckless with respect to the circumstances surrounding his conduct or the result of his conduct when he is aware of but consciously disregards a substantial and unjustifiable risk that the circumstances exist or the result will occur. The risk must be of such a nature and degree that its disregard constitutes a gross deviation from the standard of care that an ordinary person would exercise under all the circumstances as viewed from the actor's standpoint. Eight, with respect to the evidence submitted in this case concerning the defendant having been previously convicted of a felony, if he was, you are instructed that such evidence cannot be considered by you as in any manner proving or tending to prove that the defendant was in possession of a firearm on or about June 1st, 2025. Nine, count one, aggravated Now, if you find from the evidence beyond a reason

-- nWkWEjol89g @1468s  (2639 words)
   https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=nWkWEjol89g&t=1463s
   We do, Judge. May I proceed? Yes. Ladies and gentlemen of the jury, this is what the evidence will show. March 25th, it's about 1:30. It's early Saturday morning. Eric Moody, walking home, making a turn on the corner of Alamo and Provance. And suddenly, he hears something. Coming up. Coming up from the right, a white car comes out of nowhere. It hits Eric Moody so hard, it pops his legs into the air, slams him into a brick wall, and hits the metal bars the burglar bars on that building so hard that the metal bends. And who's behind the the wheel of that white car that ended Eric's life? Robert Castille. The evidence will show that that night Robert Castille went looking for trouble. And when he found trouble, and it was way too much for him to handle, he booked it out of there. And when he booked it out of there, he caused a crash that killed Eric Moody, who had nothing to do with this, 

-- _hVF9Pu_0pY @9164s  (2646 words)
   https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=_hVF9Pu_0pY&t=9159s
   Yes. So, then this was for her to appear before the grand jury on January 22nd of 2020. All right. And then the information in uh Q1, uh the witness's exhibit through her attorney, is information by Melissa Alban, the ADA that was put in the system on January 22nd, 2026. All right. So, what is it What is everybody's understanding when somebody is subpoenaed or thinks there is a valid subpoena, and they come to the DA's office, and when they come to the DA's office, they're asking to have an attorney. What What is the law on that? Everybody's understanding of the law on that. If somebody is subpoenaed, whether they think the subpoena is valid or not, it appears that the subpoena, the grand jury subpoena, that's not done properly, it appears that maybe the witness thought that this was a valid subpoena. And then that witness comes to the DA's office. So, what is everybody's understanding o
